Manchester Evening Herald Photograph Collection
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Atty Robert Pigeon appted State Atty,Tolland County, 7/2/1968; Names: Robert J. Pigeon| Topics: Clipping; Law and Lawyers (Box 2, Folder MH.207)
  - Dr. Fred McKone earns 4th degree from Uconn,Rock, 7/15/1968; Names: Fred McKone| Topics: Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.208)
  - Dixieland Concert-Rockville Henry park, 08/??/68; Topics: Entertainment; Parks (Box 2, Folder MH.209)
  - Swim Meet at Henry Park-Rockville, 08/??/68; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 2, Folder MH.210)
  - Safe found after 16 years at Vernon Police Station, 8/8/1968; Topics: Police Dept. (Box Boz 2, Folder MH.211)
  - Roy Darwin at Superior Court, 8/8/1968; Names: Roy Darwin| Topics: Law and Lawyers (Box 2, Folder MH.212)
  - Carnival at Henry Park-Rockville, 8/14/1968; Topics: Entertainment; Parks (Box 2, Folder MH.213)
  - Play area and wading pool-Henry Park-Rockville, 8/14/1968; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 2, Folder MH.214)
  - Road race at Henry Park (with ambulance)-Rockville, 8/16/1968; Topics: Police Dept.; Parks (Box 2, Folder MH.215)
  - Library party for summer reading program-Rockville, 8/23/1968; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 2, Folder MH.216)
  - Hootenanny at Henry park-Rockville, 8/16/1968; Topics: Entertainment; Parks (Box 2, Folder MH.217)
  - Talcottville Pond (with bridge)-Talcottville, 8/27/1968; Topics: Talcottville (Box 2, Folder MH.218)
  - Joggers and Runners at Henry Park-Rockville, 8/29/1968; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 2, Folder MH.219)
  - Water Carnival at Henry Park-Rockville, 8/30/1968; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 2, Folder MH.220)
  - Reception for new teachers at Middle School-Vernon, 8/30/1968; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 2, Folder MH.221)
  - Progress made on new schools (VCMS)-Vernon, 09/??/68; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 2, Folder MH.222)
  - Two teachers from Philippines teaching at RHS-Vern, 09/??/68; Topics: Schools & Education; RHS (Box 2, Folder MH.223)
  - Elderly given cookout- Exchange Club (Franklin Park), 9/13/1968; Topics: Civic Organizations; Senior Citizens (Box 2, Folder MH.224)
  - Edmund Dwyer-New Police Chief-Vernon, 9/17/1968; Names: Edmund Dwyer| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.225)
  - Senior Citizens' Center ground breaking- Vernon, 9/18/1968; Topics: Housing; Senior Citizens (Box 2, Folder MH.226)
  - New Vernon Juvenile Court-Vernon, 9/27/1968; Topics: Law and Lawyers (Box 2, Folder MH.227)
  - Senator Abraham Ribicoff in Rockville, 9/27/1968; Names: Abraham Ribicoff| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 2, Folder MH.228)
  - Vernon Police Wives' Club-Vernon, 9/28/1968; Topics: Police Dept.; Social Organizations (Box 2, Folder MH.229)
  - Cong Church "Negro Children Playing"-Talcottville, 10/??/68; Topics: Churches; Talcottville (Box 2, Folder MH.230)
  - Fenton Futtner, 10/??/68; Names: Fenton Futtner (Box 2, Folder MH.231)
  - Dr. Donald Berger-Radiology Room-Rockville, 10/??/68; Names: Donald Berger| Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 2, Folder MH.232)
  - GOP Headquarters opening at Vernon Circle, 10/4/1968; Topics: Politics & Elections; Vernon Circle (Box 2, Folder MH.233)
  - New Police Sgts: Kiellquist and Neff, 10/11/1968; Names: Kiellquist, Neff| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.234)
  - Rockville Chamber of Commerce Annual Banquet, 10/17/1968; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 2, Folder MH.235)
  - Project Concert-Vernon, 10/22/1968; Topics: Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.236)
  - Democratic Headquarters at Vernon Circle, 10/28/1968; Topics: Politics & Elections; Vernon Circle (Box 2, Folder MH.237)
  - Republican Headquarters at Vernon Circle, 10/26/1968; Topics: Politics & Elections; Vernon Circle (Box 2, Folder MH.238)
  - Cong Church-Christmas Bazzar preparations-Vernon, 10/29/1968; Topics: Churches; Vernon Center (Box 2, Folder MH.239)
  - Robert Houley-Vernon, 10/30/1968; Names: Robert Houley| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 2, Folder MH.240)
  - Sketch of Talcottville School-Talcottville, 10/31/1968; Topics: Schools & Education; Talcottville (Box 2, Folder MH.241)
  - Public Health Nurses' Retiring Party-Rockville, 11/??/68; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 2, Folder MH.242)
  - Ecumenical Youth meeting at Cong Church-Vernon, 11/5/1968; Topics: Churches (Box 2, Folder MH.243)
  - Allen Houley-Election Returns-Vernon, 11/6/1968; Names: Allen Houley| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 2, Folder MH.244)
  - Carruthers-Election Returns-Vernon, 11/6/1968; Names: Carruthers, ?| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 2, Folder MH.245)
  - New Juvenile Court Open House-Rockville, 11/8/1968; Topics: Law and Lawyers; Rockville Redevelopment (Box 2, Folder MH.246)
  - YNK Recipes-The Scarlatos, 51 Discovery Rd,Vernon, 11/14/1968; Names: Scarlato, ?| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 2, Folder MH.247)
  - Lake Street School Book Fair-Vernon, 11/14/1968; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 2, Folder MH.248)
  - Samual Pearl-Sworn onto Board of Representatives, 11/18/1968; Names: Samual Pearl| Topics: Clipping; Town Government (Box 2, Folder MH.249)
  - Good Old Days Fair-Vernon, 11/22/1968; Topics: Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.250)
  - Career Day at RHS-Rockville, 11/22/1968; Topics: RHS (Box 2, Folder MH.251)
  - Steelwork at new courthouse-Rockville, 11/22/1968; Topics: Law and Lawyers; Rockville Redevelopment (Box 2, Folder MH.252)
  - Women of the Moose prepare for bazzaar-Rockville, 11/29/1968; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 2, Folder MH.253)
  - House Feature-McCandless ,42 Echo Dr,Vernon, 11/30/1968; Names: Mr. & Mrs. John McCandless| Topics: Housing (Box 2, Folder MH.254)
  - Christmas Parade-visiting Santa's house, 12/2/1968; Names: Children| Topics: Holidays (Box 2, Folder MH.255)
  - RPL-Display of Old Christmas Cards-Rockville, 12/21/1968; Topics: Rockville Library; Holidays (Box 2, Folder MH.256)
  - Santa with Underpriveleged Children, 12/22/1968; Topics: Holidays (Box 2, Folder MH.257)
  - Robert Houley-Vernon, 12/23/1968; Names: Robert Houley| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.258)
  - New Court House-Rockville, 01/??/69; Topics: Law and Lawyers; Rockville Redevelopment (Box 2, Folder MH.259)
  - Stereo East & New Store on Rt # 30-Vernon, 1/18/1969; Topics: Businesses (Box 2, Folder MH.260)
  - Need for Furnishings-Talcottville School-Talcottville, 1/24/1969; Topics: Schools & Education; Talcottville (Box 2, Folder MH.261)
  - House of the month,Robert & Erica Pilver, Echo Mt, 1/25/1969; Names: R. & E. Pilver| Topics: Housing (Box 2, Folder MH.262)
  - Rev. Robert Wellner,new rector, St. John's Episc. Church, 1/27/1969; Names: Robert Wellner| Topics: Churches (Box 2, Folder MH.263)
  - Moira Scalley,19 Estello Rd,Miss Vernon Semi-Finalist, 1/29/1969; Names: Moira Scalley| Topics: Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.264)
  - Rockville Hospital-Babies in bassinets-Rockville, 02/??/69; Topics: Marriage & Family; Rockville Hospital (Box 2, Folder MH.265)
  - Elsie Neff retiring as Town Clerk-Rockville, 2/2/1969; Names: Elsie Neff| Topics: Town Government (Box 2, Folder MH.266)
  - Rotch at Rockville Court-Rockville, 2/5/1969; Names: Rotch, ?| Topics: Law and Lawyers (Box 2, Folder MH.267)
  - Modern dance-Paul Taylor Group at RHS, 2/7/1969; Names: Paul Taylor | Topics: RHS; Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.268)
  - Snowbound schools (RHS-Vernon Elementary), 2/13/1969; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 2, Folder MH.269)
  - Truck overturns-accident-Rockville, 2/13/1969; Topics: Police Dept.; Transportation (Box 2, Folder MH.270)
  - Skiing on Fox Hill-Rockville, 2/18/1969; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 2, Folder MH.271)
  - Publicity for Red Cross Dance-Rockville, 2/18/1969; Topics: Civic Organizations; Entertainment (Box 2, Folder MH.272)
  - Students going to Rockville High School-, 2/24/1969; Topics: RHS (Box 2, Folder MH.273)
  - Henry Building condemned(interior & interior photos), 2/26/1969; Topics: Rockville Redevelopment; Landmarks (Box 2, Folder MH.274)
  - Henry Building-exterior-Rockville, 3/4/1969; Topics: Rockville Redevelopment; Landmarks (Box 2, Folder MH.275)
  - Henry Building moving day-(interior & exterior photos), 3/11/1969; Topics: Rockville Redevelopment; Landmarks (Box 2, Folder MH.276)
  - Rockville Savings & Loan in Trailer-Rockville, 3/18/1969; Topics: Businesses; Rockville Redevelopment (Box 2, Folder MH.277)
  - Fire at Rockville Fish & Game Club-Rockville, 3/19/1969; Topics: Fire Dept.; Social Organizations (Box 2, Folder MH.278)
  - Rockville High School Science Winner-Rockville, 3/25/1969; Topics: RHS (Box 2, Folder MH.279)
  - Dedication of St. John's Episcopal Church-Vernon, 3/26/1969; Topics: Churches (Box 2, Folder MH.280)
  - Building coming down(Old Talcott Library) Talcottville, 4/1/1969; Topics: Talcottville; Landmarks (Box 2, Folder MH.281)
  - Pickets-Rockville, 4/2/1969; Topics: Labor (Box 2, Folder MH.282)
  - Fire at RHS (cafeteria & auditorium)-Rockville, 4/10/1969; Topics: RHS; Fire Dept. (Box 2, Folder MH.283)
  - Run away car-Rockville, 4/10/1969; Topics: Police Dept.; Transportation; Landmarks (Box 2, Folder MH.284)
  - House of month-Mrs. James Filkoff,10 Janet Ln, Vernon, 4/26/1969; Names: Mrs. James Filkoff| Topics: Housing (Box 2, Folder MH.285)
  - David Williams named to Board of Representatives-Vern, 5/27/1969; Names: David Williams| Topics: Clipping; Town Government (Box 2, Folder MH.286)
  - Rev. John Lacey delegate to church signed-Vernon, 6/24/1969; Names: John Lacey| Topics: Clipping; Churches (Box 2, Folder MH.287)
  - High school Chamber Ensemble-Rockville, 6/27/1969; Topics: RHS (Box 2, Folder MH.288)
  - Peter Vendrillo honored by Mayor-Vernon, 7/2/1969; Names: Peter Vendrillo (Box 2, Folder MH.289)
  - John Canavan appointed to staff position for Greater Hartford Com. College, 7/16/1969; Names: John Canavan| Topics: Schools & Education; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.290)
  - Frank McCoy endorsed for Mayor by Republicans-Vernon, 8/20/1969; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.291)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Owen Warren-50th Anniversary,35 Hillside Ave, 9/9/1969; Names: Mr. & Mrs. Warren| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 2, Folder MH.292)
  - Seymour Lavitt running for Mayor, 9/19/1969; Names: Seymour Lavitt| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.293)
  - Antoni Sadlak (photo from 1962 used with obit), 10/18/1969; Names: Antoni Sadlak| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 2, Folder MH.294)
  - David Williams-Democratic candidate-Vernon, 10/24/1969; Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.295)
  - Seymour Lavitt-running for Mayor-Vernon, 10/31/1969; Names: Seymour Lavitt| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.296)
  - Frank McCoy-running for Mayor-Vernon, 10/31/1969; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.297)
  - June Litton, 11/??/69; Names: June Litton (Box 2, Folder MH.298)
  - Tolland County Superior Court-Rockville, 11/14/1969; Topics: Law and Lawyers; Rockville Redevelopment (Box 2, Folder MH.299)
  - Robert Houley state senator, chairman March of Dimes Campaign, 1/13/1970; Names: Robert Houley| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.300)
  - Atty Harry Hammer sworn in as Deputy Secr. Of State by Ella Grasso-Secr. Of State, 1/19/1970; Names: Harry Hammer & Ella Grasso| Topics: Clipping; Law and Lawyers (Box 2, Folder MH.301)
  - Paul B. Sweeney, 2/6/1970; Names: Paul B. Sweeney (Box 2, Folder MH.302)
  - Celeste Sanborn engaged to Mr. Sherman, 2/14/1970; Names: Celeste Sanborn| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 2, Folder MH.303)
  - Edmund Parker, Pres. Of Manchester Savings Bank., 2/20/1970; Names: Edmund E. Parker| Topics: Businesses; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.304)
  - Sen. Robert Houley seeks re-election, 2/25/1970; Names: Robert Houley| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.305)
  - Robert H. Steele, 2/27/1970; Names: Robert H. Steele (Box 2, Folder MH.306)
  - Robert Houley, 3/26/1970; Names: Robert Houley (Box 2, Folder MH.307)
  - James M. Troy-VP of Vernon National Bank, 4/14/1970; Names: James M. Troy| Topics: Businesses; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.308)
  - Harry S. Godi-new Dean of Students for regional Comm. College, 4/23/1970; Names: Harry S. Godi| Topics: Schools & Education; Clipping (Box 2, Folder MH.309)
  - Scranton Motors-Building front, 5/7/1970; Topics: Businesses; Transportation (Box 2, Folder MH.310)
  - Thomas Wolff,new Pres of CT State Assn of Life Underwriters, 5/16/1970; Names: Thomas J. Wolff| Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.311)
  - Accident on I-84-Vernon, 6/1/1970; Topics: Police Dept.; Transportation (Box 3, Folder MH.312)
  - Five retiring teachers-Vernon, 6/9/1970; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.313)
  - Sister Gabrielita 50th Anniversary-Vernon, 6/10/1970; Names: Sister Gabrielita (Box 3, Folder MH.314)
  - James Sober Ex-Yale student- Vernon, 6/12/1970; Names: James Sober (Box 3, Folder MH.315)
  - High School graduation-Rockville, 6/19/1970; Topics: RHS (Box 3, Folder MH.316)
  - Squirt new fire engine-Rockville, 7/2/1970; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 3, Folder MH.317)
  - Fire at Tober Baseball Company(formerly Regan Mill)Rock., 7/2/1970; Topics: Fire Dept.; Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.318)
  - Two visiting girls from Sweden-Vernon, 7/23/1970; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.319)
  - Robert Houley-Vernon, 08/??/70; Names: Robert Houley (Box 3, Folder MH.320)
  - Sewage treatment Plant (fish death story)-Rockville, 8/5/1970; Topics: Public Health; Environment (Box 3, Folder MH.321)
  - Death of Fish-Tankeroosen River-Golf Land-Talcottville, 8/6/1970; Topics: Public Health; Environment (Box 3, Folder MH.322)
  - Antoni Sadlak, Jr.-Rockville, 8/14/1970; Names: Antoni Sadlak, Jr.| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.323)
  - Antoni Sadlak, Jr. Rep. nominee for 47th District-Rockville, 8/14/1970; Names: Antoni Sadlak, Jr.| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.324)
  - Alden Spinning Mill closing(exterior photo)-Talcottville, 8/19/1970; Topics: Talcottville; Mills and Factories (Box 3, Folder MH.325)
  - Alden Spinning Mill(interior photo)-Talcottville, 8/19/1970; Topics: Talcottville; Mills and Factories (Box 3, Folder MH.326)
  - Best swimmers, male & female, at Vernon Town Meet, 9/9/1970; Topics: Recreation; Entertainment (Box 3, Folder MH.327)
  - Tri-City Plaza-ground breaking for new addition-Vernon, 9/10/1970; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle (Box 3, Folder MH.328)
  - Election Day-Vernon, 11/4/1970; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.329)
  - Demonstrations in Central Park-Sober Trial-Rockville, 12/2/1970; Topics: Clipping; Parks; National Events (Box 3, Folder MH.330)
  - Demonstrations at Rockville Superior Court-Rockville, 12/2/1970; Topics: Clipping; National Events (Box 3, Folder MH.331)
  - Mayor Frank McCoy-Vernon, ??/??/71; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.332)
  - Fox Hill Skiing-Rockville, 01/??/71; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 3, Folder MH.333)
  - Dr. Frederick McKone elected Dir. of People's SB-Vernon, 1/2/1971; Names: Frederick McKone| Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.334)
  - Robert Steele-town not known, 1/10/1971; Names: Robert Steele (Box 3, Folder MH.335)
  - Antoni Sadlak, Jr. Assoc Prod-Bar Harbor,ME Festival, 1/28/1971; Names: Antoni Sadlak, Jr.| Topics: Clipping (Box 3, Folder MH.336)
  - Jennifer Dickens winner of the science fair-Vernon, 3/12/1971; Names: Jennifer Dickens| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.337)
  - Joseph Franek, 4/2/1971; Names: Joseph Franek (Box 3, Folder MH.338)
  - Police Chief Edmund Dwyer selected by Elks-Outstanding Citizen of the year, 4/12/1971; Names: Edmund Dwyer| Topics: Police Dept.; Clipping; Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.339)
  - Robert Steele, 5/5/1971; Names: Robert Steele (Box 3, Folder MH.340)
  - Robert J. Pigeon resigns as Tolland CT State Attny -Rockville, 5/19/1971; Names: Robert Pigeon| Topics: Clipping; Law and Lawyers (Box 3, Folder MH.341)
  - Rev. Robert H. Wellner, 6/8/1971; Names: Rev. Robert Wellner (Box 3, Folder MH.342)
  - C. Perry Chilberg Supervisor at Nelson Freighways, 6/19/1971; Names: C. Perry Chilberg| Topics: Businesses; Clipping (Box 3, Folder MH.343)
  - Miss Connecticut Reception, 8/7/1971; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.344)
  - Regals-Vernon Circle, Store front, 8/18/1971; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle (Box 3, Folder MH.345)
  - Regals-Sales Staff-Vernon Circle-Vernon, 09/??/71; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle (Box 3, Folder MH.346)
  - Henry Park swim meet-Rockville, 9/7/1971; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 3, Folder MH.347)
  - John DeQuattro-United Appeal Campaign Chair-Vernon, 12/14/1973; Names: John DeQuattro| Topics: Clipping; Civic Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.348)
  - Charles Chilberg-Nelson Freightways, new Pres of Motor Transportation Assn., 10/9/1971; Names: Charles Chilberg| Topics: Businesses; Clipping; Transportation (Box 3, Folder MH.349)
  - Thomas Wolff-campaign biography-Vernon, 10/26/1971; Names: Thomas Wolff| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 3, Folder MH.350)
  - DAS Award (Jaycees)-Vernon, 1/19/1972; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.351)
  - Mardi Gras Mural-Vernon, 2/2/1972; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.352)
  - John F. Sommers elected to Bd of Trustees-Cushing Academy, 2/10/1972; Names: John F. Sommers| Topics: Clipping (Box 3, Folder MH.353)
  - Rev Paul Bowman-Union Cong Church-Rockville, 03/??/72; Names: Paul Bowman| Topics: Churches (Box 3, Folder MH.354)
  - Rev Lyman Reed-Assoc Pastor-Union Cong Church-Rockvil, 03/??/72; Names: Lyman Reed| Topics: Churches (Box 3, Folder MH.355)
  - House Fire on Village Street-Rockville, 3/7/1972; Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 3, Folder MH.356)
  - Mark Boudreau, Rockville High-Rockville, 3/10/1972; Names: Mark Bourdreau| Topics: RHS (Box 3, Folder MH.357)
  - Route #30-Two car accident-Vernon, 3/21/1972; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 3, Folder MH.358)
  - Accident-Route 30-Vernon, 3/21/1972; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 3, Folder MH.359)
  - Donald Watrous,Organist, Union Cong Church-Rockville, 4/8/1972; Names: Donald Watrous| Topics: Churches (Box 3, Folder MH.360)
  - Amateur Art Show at Tri City Plaza-Vernon, 6/5/1972; Topics: Entertainment; Vernon Circle; Arts (Box 3, Folder MH.361)
  - David A. Bourne-elected Pres. Of Kiwanis Club of Manch., 6/14/1972; Names: David A. Bourne| Topics: Clipping; Civic Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.362)
  - High School graduation-Rockville, 6/23/1972; Topics: RHS (Box 3, Folder MH.363)
  - Don's American (gas station)-Talcottville, 7/17/1972; Topics: Businesses; Talcottville (Box 3, Folder MH.364)
  - Wayside Furniture-Rt 83-Grand Opening-Vernon, 9/7/1972; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.365)
  - Vernon Community Service Center opening-Vernon, 9/29/1972; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.366)
  - Charles Chilberg of Nelson Freightways re-elected Pres. of Motor Trans Assn., 10/18/1972; Names: Charles Chilberg| Topics: Businesses; Clipping (Box 3, Folder MH.367)
  - Potterten's TV-Vernon, 12/16/1972; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.368)
  - YMCA Teaching Course-Vernon, 1/19/1973; Topics: Schools & Education; Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.369)
  - James Cornish-Jaycees' Man of the Year, 1/25/1973; Names: James Cornish| Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.370)
  - House of the month-Mr & Mrs Warren Gottier-Talcottville, 1/27/1973; Names: Mr. & Mrs. Warren Gottier| Topics: Housing; Talcottville (Box 3, Folder MH.371)
  - Mike Hardel,Warren Hubbard-Fitzgerald Ford-Vernon, 2/15/1973; Names: Hardel, Hibbard| Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.372)
  - Not ID'd, Francis Pritchard 2nd from left-Rockville, 2/16/1973; 0 (Box 3, Folder MH.373)
  - Suburban Women's Club-Fashion Show-Vernon, 2/20/1973; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.374)
  - TriCity Plaza-Washington's Bday, Sage-Allen's-Vernon, 2/22/1973; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle; Holidays (Box 3, Folder MH.375)
  - TriCity Plaza-Washington's Bday, Grant's-Vernon, 2/22/1973; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle; Holidays (Box 3, Folder MH.376)
  - Rotary Man of the Year-Rockville, 3/5/1973; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.377)
  - Scranton Motors Salesman-Rockville, 3/9/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.378)
  - Pick-a-Color, Interior-Rt 83-Vernon, 3/12/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.379)
  - Alpine House-Vernon, 3/13/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.380)
  - L & M Equipment-Rt 83-Vernon, 3/14/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.381)
  - Potterten's TV-Vernon, 3/14/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.382)
  - Neptune Water-Bed, Route 30-Vernon, 3/14/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.383)
  - Cart Wheel-Vernon, 3/19/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.384)
  - Fitzgerald Ford-Rt 83-Vernon, 4/4/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.385)
  - Fire-Rockville, 4/10/1973; Topics: Fire Dept.; Housing (Box 3, Folder MH.386)
  - Easter Bunny-Rockville, 4/17/1973; Topics: Holidays (Box 3, Folder MH.387)
  - Leather Shop-Talcottville, 4/21/1973; Topics: Businesses; Talcottville (Box 3, Folder MH.388)
  - Gifford-Eagle Scout-Vernon, 4/27/1973; Names: Gifford, ?| Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.389)
  - Talcottville School-Arbor Day-Talcottville, 4/30/1973; Topics: Schools & Education; Talcottville; Holidays (Box 3, Folder MH.390)
  - Judy Genovesi-Youth Hockey Award-Vernon, 4/30/1973; Names: Judy Genovesi| Topics: Recreation (Box 3, Folder MH.391)
  - Clowntown Fair-Vernon, 5/2/1973; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.392)
  - Opening of Welply's Flower Shop-Vernon, 5/19/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.393)
  - Mayor Frank McCoy with signs for "Walk for Hunger", 5/31/1973; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.394)
  - RHS Graduation-Rockville, 06/??/73; Topics: Schools & Education; RHS (Box 3, Folder MH.395)
  - Rockville Senior Citizens of the Year-Rockville, 06/01?73; Topics: Senior Citizens (Box 3, Folder MH.396)
  - Vernon Teachers Retiring-Vernon, 6/2/1973; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.397)
  - Rockville Hospital Honors Its Volunteers-Rockville, 6/8/1973; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 3, Folder MH.398)
  - James M. Troy on Bd of Directors of Bughaus, Inc. Vernon, 6/18/1973; Names: James M. Troy| Topics: Clipping (Box 3, Folder MH.399)
  - Sing Lee Chinese Rest.-El Camino Plaza-Rt 30-Vernon, 6/21/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.400)
  - Fitzgerald Ford, Herb Manley & Warren Hubbard-Rockville, 7/18/1973; Names: Manley & Hubbard| Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.401)
  - Mr. & Mrs. R. Nicola-18 Stephen St,Vernon-25th Annivers., 7/18/1973; Names: R. Nicola| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 3, Folder MH.402)
  - Casa Nova restaurant-Vernon, 8/9/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.403)
  - Panel World-Vernon, 8/21/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.404)
  - Carl's TV-Vernon, 8/21/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.405)
  - Adam's Apple Furniture-Vernon, 8/21/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.406)
  - Steve and Tom's Pizzaria-Vernon, 10/25/1973; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.407)
  - Mayor Frank McCoy and wife on Election Day-Vernon, 11/??/73; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.408)
  - Talcottville Church Quilting Party-Talcottville, 11/23/1973; Topics: Churches; Talcottville (Box 3, Folder MH.409)
  - Rev Kenneth Knox-Talcottville Cong Church-Talcottville, 12/5/1973; Names: Kenneth Knox| Topics: Churches; Talcottville (Box 3, Folder MH.410)
  - John O'Connell, 01/??/74; 0 (Box 3, Folder MH.411)
  - Betsy Steele (wife of Robert)-Vernon, 2/9/1974; 0 (Box 3, Folder MH.412)
  - Tom Dooley-Vernon Republicann-Vernon, 3/18/1974; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.413)